Damjan Pjević

damjan.pjevic@gmail.com

+386 40 933 622

www.pjevic.com

linkedin.com/in/damjan-pjevic/

An ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused on Digital Communication and history in the computer software industry, I am currently in pursuit of a master's degree in Business Informatics at the Economics Faculty of Liubliana, Experienced in working with the clients. public speaking and working in a team and showed a history of working in the fields of programming, telecommunications, event organisation, digital media, social media and marketing.

SKILLS

IT: Website management, basics in mobile application development, basics in telecommunications.

Programming: Java, JavaScript, C#, Python, HTML, CSS, Android Studio, Unity, WordPress.

Basics in marketing and PR: Content creation, Managing social media, Verbal communication, Promotions.

Other: event organisation, working in a team, working under pressure, communication skill.

Languages: English C2, Slovenian C2, Serbian B2, German B1, Russian A1.

Multiple years of experience in Adobe Creative Cloud, Office Suite.

European driving license - AM, B, B1 (since 2014), International driving licence.

EXPERIENCES

2019-2020	Website manager at Value Add Games : Updating and maintaining the website and the online shop (using WordPress, WooCommerce), producing multimedia content for different campaigns. Helped with their most successful marketing campaign. Assisted with sales and helped with smaller programming tasks in Python.
2019	Programmer at Jozef Stefan Institute , Department of Intelligent Systems – Using Python and basics in auto-encoders worked on a project that builds on Sandberg's paper - Dissolving the Fermi Paradox.
2019	Took part in the <i>BEST Summer Course</i> in Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its success.
2017	Selected as one of the top 20 out of 350 global teams in OnePlus Student Marketing Challenge.
2016-2019	LMMFE Video Team – Broadcasting/Technical assistant at a couple of events in cooperation with RTV SLO.
2016	Regional winners in global competition OSCE Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool for challenging violent extremism.
2015-2016	International Student Organisation EESTEC - LC Ljubljana.

- - As one of the Coordinators, successfully managed the PR group for EESTEC Competition for Android 2015 and reached out to more students than any year before.
 - Took part in a week-long seminar in Istanbul, Turkey focused on Marketing and Multimedia.
- Selected Class Projects: 2015-2019
 - Extension of the Pan-European Mobile Emergency Application with extended reality (Thesis project) technologies used: WebXR, Android Studio, Java, JavaScript.
 - Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.
 - Developed a standalone videogame in *Unity*.
- High School Debate club .: 2015-2019
 - Took part in three different YouthPass Exchanges all focused on international Peer-to-Peer communication.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022	Business Informatics – Master's.
	School of Economics and Business, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia
2015-2019	Multimedia Engineering – Bachelor's. Average grade: 9.0
	Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia
	Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)